greedyshemales.com 2014-11-17

# Privacy Policy

**PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT**

Visitors to our site and services will have multiple manners of interactivity with us. Depending upon your level of interaction, we will collect different information about you. The type of information collected is as follows: A. Members 

Members are those users who interact with our services in a way which requires registration, such as by uploading content to the Site. Members will be prompted to provide their e-mail address in the process of registering a username. B. Browsers

Browsers are visitors to the site who never enter into any active data collection pages. Browsers may, however, view content uploaded by Members. Any information gathered from Browsers is also gathered from Members. This information is restricted to cookies, IP Addresses and Referral URLs, and other passive information gathering devises (explained below). 

**Data Usage**

We may use your information to provide you with certain features and to create a personalized experience on the Website. We may also use that information to operate, maintain and improve features and functionality of the Website. 

We will not use your e-mail address or other personal information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent. We may use your e-mail without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes. 

We use cookies, web beacons and other information to store information so that you will not have to re-enter it on future visits, provide personalized content and information, monitor the effectiveness of the Website and monitor aggregate metrics such as the number of visitors and page views (including for use in monitoring visitors from affiliates). They may also be used to provide targeted advertising based on your country of origin and other personal information. 

We may aggregate your personal information with personal information of other members and users, and disclose such information to advertisers and other third-parties for marketing and promotional purposes. 

Your username may be displayed to other users alongside content you upload, including videos, comments and messages. 

Any videos that you submit may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels and may be viewed by the general public.

**DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**

if under duty to do so greedyshemales.com may release data to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce our Terms Of Service and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property or safety of greedyshemales.com or our subscribers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations including the police and governmental authorities for the purposes of protection against fraud or any other kind of illegal activity whether or not identified in the Terms Of Service. It is greedyshemales.com's policy, whenever possible and legally permissible, to promptly notify you upon an obligation to supply data to any third party. 

Should you deliberately upload any illegal material Greedyshemales.com shall forward all available information to all relevant authorities and this without notice. 

\- We do not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. 

**SECURITY**

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen a password) which enables you to access certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. greedyshemales.com uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to greedyshemales.com and you do so at your own risk.
